<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eason Study Blog</title>
    <link>https://Eason366.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Eason Study Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 00:27:10 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Eason366.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Guide</title>
      <link>https://Eason366.github.io/post/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 00:27:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Eason366.github.io/post/markdown/</guid>
      <description>Overview Nearly all Markdown applications support the basic syntax outlined in John Gruber’s original design document. There are minor variations and discrepancies between Markdown processors — those are noted inline wherever possible.
Headings To create a heading, add number signs (#) in front of a word or phrase. The number of number signs you use should correspond to the heading level. For example, to create a heading level three (), use three number signs (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Upload my Blog to Github</title>
      <link>https://Eason366.github.io/post/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 19:28:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Eason366.github.io/post/blog/</guid>
      <description>How to Upload my Blog to Github Upload local server  hugo server -t m10c --buildDrafts Use http://localhost:1313/ to check.
Upload to my Github hugo --theme=m10c --baseUrl=&amp;quot;https://Eason366.github.io/&amp;quot; --buildDrafts #Create web page cd public #Enter the public folder git add . git commit -m #&amp;quot;commit&amp;quot; git push -u origin master  Use https://eason366.github.io/ to check.
Creat a new Blog hugo new post/#BlogName.md </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regression Analysis on Wine Qualit</title>
      <link>https://Eason366.github.io/post/project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 02:24:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Eason366.github.io/post/project/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The study of interest was with regards to the factors that affect the quality of red wine. The data used was obtained from https://archive.ics.uci.edu/ml/machine-learning-databases/wine-quality/. For the study, quality was therefore used as the dependent variable, while independent variables used were; residual sugar, chlorides, total sulfur dioxide, pH, sulphates, and alcohol. To identify if the independent variables were significant predictors of quality, multiple linear regression was carried out using R.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
