<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Study Blog</title>
    <link>https://Eason366.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Study Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Eason366.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sorting Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://Eason366.github.io/p/sorting-algorithm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Eason366.github.io/p/sorting-algorithm/</guid>
      <description>Sorting Algorithm  1. Bubble Sort  1.1 Time Complexity 1.2 Code   2. Selection Sort  2.1 Time Complexity 2.2 Code   3. Insertion Sort  3.1 Time Complexity 3.2 Code    1.Bubble Sort 1.1 Time Complexity    Time Complexity Value     Best $O(n)$   Worse $O(n^2)$   Average $O(n^2)$    1.2 Code public class BubbleSort implements IArraySort { @Override public int[] sort(int[] sourceArray) throws Exception { int[] arr = Arrays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plane War</title>
      <link>https://Eason366.github.io/p/plane-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 10:02:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Eason366.github.io/p/plane-war/</guid>
      <description>Plane War Game Program Introduction I always think that interest is the best teacher. It is easier for us to learn what we are interested in. Especially after learning object-oriented and class programming, I have always wanted to create something, and games are undoubtedly a good choice. First of all because I like playing games very much. Secondly, because the game has very good visual effects. I believe everyone wants to have a game of their own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSE 385 Database</title>
      <link>https://Eason366.github.io/p/cse-385-database/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 17:24:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Eason366.github.io/p/cse-385-database/</guid>
      <description>2021-01-28   Create a Table CREATE TABLE dbo.tblFriends( friendId INT NOT NULL PRIMARY KEY IDENTITY, firstName VARCHAR(20) NOT NULL, lastName VARCHAR(20) NOT NULL, age INT NOT NULL DEFAULT(-1), phoneNumber VARCHAR(20) NOT NULL DEFAULT(&amp;#39;(***) ***-****&amp;#39;), [address] VARCHAR(200) NULL DEFAULT(NULL) );   Version 1: Creates many transactions INSERT INTO tblFriends (firstName, lastName, age, phoneNumber, [address]) VALUES(&amp;#39;A&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;A&amp;#39;, 22, &amp;#39;A&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;A&amp;#39;) INSERT INTO tblFriends (firstName, lastName, age, phoneNumber) VALUES (&amp;#39;B&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;B&amp;#39;, 22, &amp;#39;B&amp;#39;) INSERT INTO tblFriends (firstName, lastName, age) VALUES (&amp;#39;C&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;C&amp;#39;, 22) INSERT INTO tblFriends (firstName, lastName) VALUES (&amp;#39;D&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;D&amp;#39;) /* INSERT INTO tblFriends (firstName)VALUES (&amp;#39;E&amp;#39;) Cannot insert the value NULL into column &amp;#39;lastName&amp;#39;, table &amp;#39;Example.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Guide</title>
      <link>https://Eason366.github.io/p/markdown-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 00:27:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Eason366.github.io/p/markdown-guide/</guid>
      <description>Overview Headings Bold Italic Bold and Italic Blockquotes Lists Horizontal Rules Links Images Reference Table  Overview Nearly all Markdown applications support the basic syntax outlined in John Gruber’s original design document. There are minor variations and discrepancies between Markdown processors — those are noted inline wherever possible.
Headings To create a heading, add number signs (#) in front of a word or phrase. The number of number signs you use should correspond to the heading level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Upload my Blog to Github</title>
      <link>https://Eason366.github.io/p/how-to-upload-my-blog-to-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 19:28:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Eason366.github.io/p/how-to-upload-my-blog-to-github/</guid>
      <description>How to Upload my Blog to Github Upload local server hugo server -t hugo-theme-stack --buildDrafts Use http://localhost:1313/ to check.
Upload to my Github hugo --theme=hugo-theme-stack --baseUrl=&amp;#34;https://Eason366.github.io/&amp;#34; --buildDrafts #Create web page cd public #Enter the public folder git add . git commit -m &amp;#34;commit&amp;#34; git push -u origin master Use https://eason366.github.io/ to check.
Creat a new Blog hugo new post/#BlogName.md </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regression Analysis on Wine Qualit</title>
      <link>https://Eason366.github.io/p/regression-analysis-on-wine-qualit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 02:24:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Eason366.github.io/p/regression-analysis-on-wine-qualit/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Exploratory Analysis Model Choose Model Assumption Model and Analysis Conclusion References Appendix  Introduction The study of interest was with regards to the factors that affect the quality of red wine. The data used was obtained from https://archive.ics.uci.edu/ml/machine-learning-databases/wine-quality/. For the study, quality was therefore used as the dependent variable, while independent variables used were; residual sugar, chlorides, total sulfur dioxide, pH, sulphates, and alcohol. To identify if the independent variables were significant predictors of quality, multiple linear regression was carried out using R.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
